Don't...
（鮮血(せんけつ)）やめろ やめてくれ
Please, don't!
Don't!
やめろ〜！
Senketsu!
（流子(りゅうこ)）鮮血！
We're late, we're late!
（マコ）遅刻だ 遅刻だ
遅刻だ 遅刻だよ〜
Hurry up and get
dressed too, Ryuuko!
流子ちゃんも早く着替えて
What am I gonna do?!
（マコ）どうしよう
ヤバイよ ヤバイよ…
Calm down, Mako!
（流子）落ち着け マコ
今 朝の４時だぞ
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
It's 4AM.
Help me!
（鮮血）助けてくれ〜！
（流子）ん？
（マコ）大変だ 大変だ
大変だ 大変だ〜
Help me! I'm being murdered!
（鮮血）助けてくれ 殺される！
Mako, your lunch is ready
and waiting in the kitchen!
（好代(すくよ)）マコ お弁当は
台所に置いてあるわよ
せ… 鮮血！
Senketsu!
Good morning, Ryuuko!
あら おはよう 流子ちゃん
...Good morning...
Wait, that's my uniform!
おはようございます
てか おばさん これ私の制服
I know!
そうよ〜 ずいぶん
汚れてたみたいだから—
It was filthy, so I'm giving it
an extra-thorough cleaning!
特に念入りに洗ってるのよ
Ma'am, I can take it
—from here, so don't—
おばさん あとは私がやるんで
Nothing doing!
（好代）ダメ！
（鮮血）ギャー！
It's a student's duty to
go to school and study!
学生の本分は何？
学校に行くこと
And it's a housewife's duty to
stay home and do the laundry!
主婦の本分は何？
洗濯すること
（鮮血）ギャッ！
Is that clear?
（好代）わかったら
（鮮血）ギャッ
Now, hurry up and eat your breakfast, or you'll be late for school!
（好代）早くご飯 食べて
（鮮血）ギャッ
（好代）遅刻しちゃうわよ
But I can't go to school
...without that uniform...
（流子）遅刻ったって
その制服がなきゃ…
Oops, I forgot to panic!
Today's the big day, Ryuuko!
あ〜！ 慌てるの忘れてた
今日は流子ちゃん“あの日”よ
Big day?
あの日？
What?! Ryuuko,
you're on "that day"?!
（薔薇蔵(ばらぞう)･又郎(またろう)）何？
流子ちゃん あの日？
You're fine in your PJs! Just move!
（マコ）もう パジャマの
ままでいいから
We'll drop off your uniform later!
（薔薇蔵）
制服は あとで届けてやるから
Don't worry about a thing!
（又郎）安心しなよ
Ryuuko, wait! You're the
only one who can hear me!
流子 待て
私の言葉は流子にしか
聞こえないのだ
So please don't leave me!
I'm begging you!
（鮮血）
だから置いていかないでくれ
頼む！ ギャー！
Are you okay, Senketsu?
大丈夫か？ 鮮血
"Senketsu"? What's that?
鮮血？ 何それ
You gave your uniform a name?
流子ちゃん
服に名前 付けてんの？
Wow, you must really be lonely!
もう 寂しがり屋なんだから
Wait!
All the more reason to go to school! There's lots of friends there!
それじゃ なおのこと
学校 行かなきゃ
友達でいっぱいだよ
There's nothing but enemies,
and you know it!
（流子）敵しかいねえだろうが！
In we go!
（マコ）そ〜れ〜
（流子）うわ〜
Sorry, Senketsu!
（流子）すまん 鮮血
（鮮血）ああ 流子！
流子！ ああ…
Ryuuko! Ryuuko!
Actually, this is surprisingly pleasant.
意外と気持ちがいい
...The wrinkles...
...The wrinkles are melting away...
しわが… しわが伸びて
伸びて… ああ〜
Melting away... Ahh.
ハァ〜
What's with this mass migration?
一体 何なんだ この民族大移動は
There is a day when all of Honnouji Academy's No-Stars put their youth on the line when they go to school.
（マコ）本能字(ほんのうじ)学園の
無星生徒たちが—
青春の全てを懸けて学校に向かう日
That day has dawned!
Today is that day!
そう まさに今日が 今日こそが
This is No-Late Day!
“ノー遅刻デー”よ
EPISODE 4
DAWN OF A
MISERABLE MORNING
This is a world tailored to someone's whims and fancies
dareka ga katteni kimeta readymade na
I'll break free of its shackles
kyou wo nugisutete
RYUUKO
MATOI
And sprint toward my goal
hadashi de hashitte iku
Even if I lose my way
machigattatte
GAMAGOORI IRA
SANAGEYAMA UZU
JAKUZURE NONON
INUMUTA HOUKA
Or trip and fall
korondatte
INUMUTA HOUKA
MANKANSHOKU FAMILY
Those wounds will still create
surimuita itami mo
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
MIKISUGI
AIKUROU
KINAGASE
TSUMUGU
An original future for me
original na ashita ni naru
KIRYUUIN
SATSUKI
I hold my destiny in my own hands
tsukiageta kono te ni nigirishimeta
And it shines ever so brightly
chikai ga hikari ni natte
So until the day I reach you
itsuka kimi ni todoku sono shunkan made
I don't have the time to sit around crying
naiteru hima nante nai kara
My burning passion pours out from within me
hamidashite shimatta atsui omoi ga
And shines like a star in the night sky
yozora de kagayaki dasu
I think I now understand
umarete kita imi ga
Why I was born
wakatta ki ga shita
I'll make all of my dreams come true
negaigoto wa zenbu kono te de
With my own hands
kanaeru
あ… ノー遅刻デー？ 何だそりゃ
"No-Late Day"?
What the heck is that?
（蟇郡(がまごおり)）ハハハハハ
戸惑っているな 纏(まとい)流子
I can see that you are
confused, Matoi Ryuuko!
You're that jerk from
—the Four Devas—
貴様 四天王の！
One of Honnouji Academy's
Student Council Devas!
本能字学園
生徒会四天王の１人…
Discliplinary Bureau Chairman, Gamagoori Ira!
DISCIPLINARY
BUREAU
CHAIRMAN
GAMAGOORI
IRA
Allow me to explain!
（蟇郡）ならば教えてやろう
No-Late Day is a school event that comes once a semester
ノー遅刻デーとは１学期に一度
抜き打ちで我ら風紀部が—
in which the Disciplinary Bureau whips
unsuspecting No-Star slackers into shape!
ふぬけた無星の生徒に活を入れる
学校行事のことだ
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
When the siren goes off
in the slums at 4AM,
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
朝４時に貧民窟にサイレンが
鳴り響いたとき 無星生徒は—
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
the No-Stars must evade the traps that we at the
Disciplinary Bureau built with our technological prowess
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
TRAP
DROP
OUT
LATE
TRAP
DROP
OUT
LATE
TRAP
DROP
OUT
LATE
TRAP
DROP
OUT
LATE
TRAP
我々風紀部が その技術の粋を
凝らして築き上げた—
TRAP
LATE
幾多のワナを突破して
始業ベルの鳴る８時30分までに
登校せねばならぬ
and make it to school by the time
the first period bell rings at 8:30AM!
DISCIPLINE
万一 遅刻した場合は—
Should they arrive late,
DISCIPLINE
即刻退学だ！ って貴様！
—they are expelled on the spot and—
What the hell?!
What manner of
slacker outfit is that?!
何をふぬけた格好をしている
うっ！ か… 神衣(かむい)は今 洗濯中だ
もうすぐ届く
My Godrobe's in the laundry!
It'll be dropped off soon!
（蟇郡）フン 言い訳はよせ
Spare me your excuses.
Leaving for school in a
slovenly outfit like that
そんな だらしない姿で
学園に向かうとは—
学園に 皐月(さつき)様に対して…
is a mortal insult to not only the
academy, but also Lady Satsuki herself!
MORTAL
INSULT
Is it, though?!
（マコ）そうでしょうか
（蟇郡）ん？
Ryuuko was asleep until just now!
（マコ）流子ちゃんは
今まで寝てたんです
寝てる人がパジャマを
着てるのは当然です
It's perfectly normal for
sleeping people to wear pajamas!
それを笑うことは
誰にもできません
No one can laugh at that!
Or do you mean to say that you
sleep in your uniform, Gamagoori?
それとも蟇郡先輩は寝てるときも
その格好なんですか？
（蟇郡）いや 俺は裸だ
No, I sleep in the nude.
（マコ）裸じゃ風邪をひきます
（女子生徒）あ〜 裸…
今 裸って…
You'll catch a cold if
you sleep in the buff!
風邪をひいていて—
If you get sick, do you think you'll be able to
work to your fullest potential in an emergency?
（女子生徒）あ〜 裸…
今 裸って…
いざというときに
力が発揮できますか？
いや〜 裸…
（蟇郡）おっ おう
...W-Well...
Please sleep in pajamas
like everyone else!
（マコ）蟇郡先輩も
寝るときはパジャマを着てください
What is your name?
貴様 名前は？
Mankanshoku Mako, Class 2-A!
２年甲組 満艦飾(まんかんしょく)マコ
The pattern on my favorite pajamas is one Mt. Fuji, two hawks, and three eggplants!
好きなパジャマ柄は
一富士二鷹(たか)三なすびです
満艦飾か 覚えておこう
Mankanshoku, you say?
I'll remember that.
Matoi!
纏！ 貴様が今
何を着ていようが構いはしない
I couldn't care less what you
happen to be wearing right now!
But do you think you can reach
the school without your Godrobe?
だが 果たして神衣なしの貴様が
無事に学校にたどりつけるかな
Behold the Disciplinary
Bureau's mighty barrier!
我が風紀部 こん身の関門
刮目(かつもく)して見よ！
Shocker!
おったまげ〜！
Look, Ryuuko!
見て 流子ちゃん！
町が遊園地みたいになってるよ
It's like the whole city's been
turned into an amusement park!
I've never seen anything
like this before!
こんなの初めてだよ
うわ〜！ そして流子ちゃん
始業まで あと３時間しかないよ
And there's only three hours to go until our first class, Ryuuko!
フン 何だかんだと
御託の多い学校だぜ
The people at this school sure love to hear themselves talk.
All right. Challenge accepted.
わかったよ やってやるよ
I'm gonna bust through every
last one of the traps you bozos made!
てめえらが作ったワナ
全部ぶっ潰して登校してやらあ！
As you wish! Students,
commence commute!
いいだろう！
全員 登校開始だ！
Forward march!
進め〜！
Mako, don't get separated!
（流子）マコ 離れるな
（マコ）うん
'Kay!
A trap right off the bat, huh?
（流子）早速トラップってわけか
（マコ）わ〜 落ちる 落ちるよ〜
I'm falling! I'm falling!
（流子）よいしょっと
Up you go!
CHECKPOINT
第１チェックポイント
通過おめでとう
Congratulations on
passing the first checkpoint!
I neglected to mention that use of the
No-Star commuter cable cars is prohibited!
言い忘れていたが—
無星通学用のケーブルカーは
使用禁止だ
Obey the rules and stick
to the prescribed route!
規則正しく順路を守るがいい
And now, gentlemen,
until we meet again at school!
では諸君 学校でお会いしよう
There's another 999 of these to go! That's way more than usual!
こんなのが あと999個も
いつもより多い
ふざけたマネを
急ぐぞ マコ！ うっ！
He's screwing with us.
Come on, Mako!
（麻衣子(まいこ)）ああ〜
Ow, that hurts so much!
（麻衣子）痛たたた〜
（マコ）あなたはクラスメイトの…
You're our classmate,
Oogure Maiko!
CLASSMATE
OOGURE
MAIKO
あんた大丈夫か？
腕ケガしてるじゃないか
Are you okay?
Your arm looks injured!
Why, it's Mankanshoku.
満艦飾さんと
あなたは転校生の纏さん
And you're Matoi,
the transfer student!
Yes, I hurt my arm
in that trap just now.
ええ 実は
さっきのトラップで腕を…
でも大丈夫
But I'll live!
I can't give up over
something like this!
こんなことで
諦めるわけにはいかないもの
Hey, don't overdo it!
あんま無理すんな
Ryuuko! Maiko's hurt,
so let's take her with us to school!
ねえ 流子ちゃん
麻衣子ちゃん ケガしてるし
学校まで一緒に行ってあげようよ
No, I can't let you!
I'd only slow you down!
そんな！
あなたたちの足手まといに
なるわけにはいかないわ
Oh, okay. We'll go on ahead, then.
Don't push yourself too hard, okay?
そっか じゃあ先 行くが
あんま むちゃすんなよ
The pain!
（麻衣子）ああっ ちょっ 痛！
頑張るのよ 麻衣子
Hang in there, Maiko!
If anyone can make it
on her own, it's you!
あなたなら１人だって行けるわ！
Ryuuko!
流子ちゃん
...For crying out loud...
Putting on a brave act, eh?
ったく 素直じゃねえな
Hold on tight.
We'll make it to school together.
（流子）ほら つかまれ
（マコ）わ〜い わ〜い
一緒に登校すんぞ
Thank you, Matoi!
（麻衣子）ありがとう 纏さん
（流子）気にすんな
Don't sweat it.
I've got nothing against
girls who put on a brave face.
無理して強がる女は
嫌いじゃねえんだよ
Ryuuko, look at that!
ねえ 流子ちゃん 見て
Isn't that the second
checkpoint up ahead?
あそこにあるの
第２チェックポイントじゃない？
How the heck are we
meant to get up there?!
って どうやって登るの？
（流子）ハハハ ちくちょう
Damn it. If I had Senketsu,
that hill would be nothing.
鮮血さえありゃ こんな坂
Move it! Make way!
（薔薇蔵）どけ どけ どけ〜い！
闇医者 薔薇蔵様のお通りだい！
BACK-ALLEY DOCTOR
Barazou the back-alley
doctor is coming through!
BACK-ALLEY DOCTOR
Anybody who doesn't get out of the way gets a Caesarian, men included!
どかねえヤツは男だろうが
帝王切開だ〜
BACK-ALLEY DOCTOR
（又郎）うおっ！
ありゃ流子の姉御
That's Ryuuko up there!
（薔薇蔵）お〜い
制服 持ってきたぞ〜
Hey, we've got your uniform!
BACK-ALLEY DOCTOR
ううっ 腕の力が…
...I can't hold on any more...
（流子）麻衣子 おい大丈夫か？
Maiko! Are you okay?!
It's no use!
あっ ダメ ああ〜
おい どこ つかんでんだ
Oops!
Hey! Watch what you're grabbing!
Keep your eyes on the road
when you're driving, you fool!
（鮮血）貴様！
運転中によそ見するな！
Dad! Are you all right?!
父ちゃん 大丈夫か？
父さんは もうダメだ
...Your dad is done for...
Matarou, I have a favor to
...ask of you, man-to-man...
又郎 お前を
男と見込んで頼みがある
この服を…
—Take this uniform and—
You got it!
わかった！ 俺が必ず
姉御にこの服を届ける
（薔薇蔵）ぐわっ！
I'll make sure Ryuuko gets
her clothes, safe and sound!
わかった！ 俺が必ず
姉御にこの服を届ける
Rest in peace, Dad!
I'll take it from here!
あとは任せて安らかに眠りな
待ってろ 流子の姉御！
Hang on, Ryuuko!
Ouch!
（麻衣子）あっ痛！
（マコ）うっ
Are you okay?!
（流子）大丈夫か！
（流子）ハァ ハァ…
Ooh! Cheese!
あっ チーズだ！
Cheese, cheese, cheese!
チーズだ チーズだ
チーズ チーズ…
Cheese, cheese, cheese, cheese, cheese!
Ahhh
Mako, look out!
マコ 危な〜い！
Ahhh
It's a pie! A pie!
うわっ パイだ！
That looks delicious, Ryuuko!
流子ちゃん おいしそう
（流子）よっと
Ow!
（麻衣子）えい！
（麻衣子）あっ痛！
（流子）おっ 大丈夫か…
—Are you okay—
You can do it, Ryuuko!
（マコ）頑張れ〜 流子ちゃ〜ん
Damn it, I could really use
Senketsu right about now!
（流子）クソッ こんなとき
鮮血があれば…
うお〜！ 流子の姉御！
Ryuuko!
Hey, that's her! I'll be right there!
とっ あれは姉御！
今 行くぜ！
My arm!
（麻衣子）う… 腕が！
（流子）大丈夫か？ ひゃっ！
Are you okay?
What a feast for the eyes!
（又郎）ご…
ごちそうさんっす アハハ〜
あっ ぐはっ
Keep your eyes on
the road, confound it!
（鮮血）だから
運転中によそ見するなよ
（ガッツ）ガッツ
Guts? Is that you, boy?
...I'm done for...
ガッツか 俺はもうダメだ
Guts, I have a favor to
...ask of you, man-to-dog...
ガッツ お前を雄と
見込んで頼みがある
（ガッツ）ガッツ ガッツ！
Stop it, you foul mutt!
Ow! That hurts!
（鮮血）おい バカ犬！
痛っ 痛っ！
Don't bite down so hard, damn it!
あんまり歯を立てるんじゃねえ
（ガッツ）ガ〜ッツ！
What time is it?
（流子）今 何時だ？
（麻衣子）８時
8AM. So we have half an hour left.
（麻衣子）ということは残り30分
厳しいかもしれない
This might be difficult.
No! No! If we don't do something,
I won't be able to go to school anymore!
このままじゃマコ
学校 行けなくなっちゃうよ〜
Hey, Maiko, what's that?
おい 麻衣子 何だありゃ
Pseudo-homeroom.
（麻衣子）疑似ホームルーム
Students who have given up
on making it to school on time,
ここまでで到底 間に合わないと
諦めた生徒たちが—
unable to face the reality that they will be kicked out of their school and homes alike tomorrow,
あしたになれば放校されて—
家も追い出される現実を
直視できず—
take attendance
with dead, vacant eyes.
うつろな目をしたまま
うつろに出席を取るの
That's too sad for words.
（流子）そいつは悲しすぎるな
So this means that the condo district
up ahead is gonna be even tougher, huh?
じゃあ こっから先の
マンション区画は—
もっとキッツいってことか
Hey, a school bus is coming!
おっ スクールバスが出てんぞ
It's a minefield!
わっ 地雷原だ
（麻衣子）
でも装甲車だから大丈夫
さすが 一つ星生徒用バスね
It's an armored vehicle,
though, so don't worry.
The One-Stars get
some cool stuff, huh?
It's passing the checkpoint!
（マコ）チェックポイントを
通過してる
No way! They have it so easy!
ウソ〜 超楽々だ〜
あれ乗りたい 乗りたい
乗りたいよ〜
I wanna ride that!
I wanna ride, I wanna ride!
Oh, the pain!
（麻衣子）うっ 痛〜い
（クラクション）
You damned No-Star!
—Get off the road! Move it—
（男子生徒）こら無星！
道を開けんか！ さっさ…
Right, then! All aboard!
（流子）お〜し乗れ乗れ！
乗っちゃれ〜い
（マコ）
やっほ〜 イエ〜イ
Hang on, Maiko, do you have a license?
（流子）おい 麻衣子
免許 持ってんのか？
Honnou Town is the private
property of the Kiryuuin family.
（麻衣子）この本能町(ほんのうちょう)は
鬼龍院(きりゅういん)家の私有地
If she has Lady Satsuki's permission, even a student can drive!
皐月様の許可があれば
学生でも運転できるんです
私も負けたくない
I don't want to lose either!
無星には無星の
意地があるってとこ見せたいの！
I want to show them that even we No-Stars have our pride!
Maiko, you can be pretty
bad-ass, you know that?
（流子）麻衣子 お前も結構やるな
（マコ）行け行け〜！
No-Star students have
hijacked a One-Star school bus.
（女性）無星生徒が
一つ星スクールバスを奪取
They're making it
through the traps.
トラップをクリアしています
...Prevent them from reaching school...
with extreme prejudice.
（スピーカー:一つ星生徒）
全力で登校を阻止しろ
Okey-dokey!
あ よいしょ
What the hell is going on?!
（流子）どうなってんだ こりゃあ！
Are preparations for the
final trap proceeding to schedule?
（蟇郡）
最終トラップの準備は順調か？
No one's here?
誰もいないのか
Wow, you gotta hand it
to these armored buses!
フゥ〜 さすがは装甲車バスだな
Time for us to strike back!
（麻衣子）反撃するのよ
（流子）えっ どうやって？
How?
ポチっとな
With this!
キャ〜 流子ちゃん
これ超楽しいよ
Ryuuko, this is way fun!
It's not safe up there,
Mako! Come down!
（流子）危ねえから降りろ マコ
...Feels so good...
快感
RPG!
（麻衣子）ＲＰＧ
Retract turret!
銃座 降ろせ！
Gosh, the view's so much clearer now!
見晴らしがよくなったね
あと少しで二つ星住宅街よ
Just a little further and we'll
be in the Two-Star district!
RPGs from either side!
（麻衣子）左右からＲＰＧ
Step on it!
（流子）飛ばせ！
（流子）痛(いて)ててて あ？
みんな起きろ
...Ouch...
Wake up, everybody!
We did it, you guys!
We made it! It's the school!
おい みんな やった
やったぞ 学校だ！
As long as we can reach our classroom in
the next fifteen minutes, we'll be on time!
（麻衣子）あと15分で
教室まで行けば間に合いますね
Awesome! That'll be a piece of cake!
（流子）よっしゃ 余裕だぜ
（マコ）余裕だぜ
Piece of cake!
We couldn't have done it
without you, Maiko!
麻衣子 お前のおかげだ
見直したぜ！
I'm seeing you in a whole new light!
Nonsense. You did all the hard work.
Still, I'm happy you think so!
そんな とても流子さんには…
でも うれしい
（流子）てれるな
（マコ）わ〜 みんな友達だね
Shucks!
Yay, we're all friends!
（ガッツ）ガチョ〜ン
Look, Ryuuko! Guts has
brought you your uniform!
見て見て 流子ちゃん
ガッツが制服を運んできてくれたよ
Hey, Guts!
（マコ）お〜い ガッツ！
（ガッツ）ワン！
Why is Guts bringing it?
なんでガッツのヤツが？
ったく おじさん何考えてんだ
Geez, what was your dad thinking?
Oh, the pain!
あっ 痛い！ ああ〜
（鮮血）わ〜 滑る 滑る
滑る 滑る
We're sliding, we're sliding!
あっ どこ行くんだ ガッツ
Where are you going, Guts?
What?
何！ 麻衣子 お前！
Maiko, what are you doing?!
You let your guard down, Ryuuko.
油断したわね 流子さん いや—
Or should I say... Matoi Ryuuko?
纏流子！ 私はずっと
このときを待っていたのよ！
I've been waiting for
this moment for ages!
麻衣子ちゃん？
Maiko?
This injured No-Star classmate
was but a fake identity!
ケガをした無星の
クラスメイトとは仮の姿
...My true identity...
その正体こそ—
is Oogure Maiko, Head of Trap Development at the Disciplinary Bureau!
本能字学園 風紀部
トラップ開発部長 大暮(おおぐれ)麻衣子さ
HEAD OF TRAP
DEVELOPMENT
OOGURE
MAIKO
（マコ）え？
（流子）トラップ開発だと？
Trap development, huh?
That's right!
そうさ ふだんは
一般生徒に混じって—
A shadowy figure who remains
undercover among the common students,
彼らの動向を探り
spying on their behavior
and developing traps!
トラップを開発する陰の存在
それがトラップ開発部長
That is the Head of Trap Development!
でも そんな生活に—
But I had grown sick
and tired of that life.
うんざりしてたんだ
そんなとき
監視モニター越しに—
I had a flash of inspiration
お前と蟇郡の会話を聞いて
ひらめいたのさ
when I overheard your conversation with
Gamagoori over the surveillance cameras.
I would steal the Godrobe, an Ultima Uniform which possessed the power
皐月様と互角に
渡り合う力を秘めた—
to go toe-to-toe
with Lady Satsuki herself.
神衣とかいう極(ごく)制服を
奪ってやろうってね
NO
-
ST
AR
With that uniform,
—I could become a Two-Star—
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
この神衣を使えば私が二つ星
いや 四天王の職に—
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
NO
-
ST
AR
ONE-STAR
NO
-
ST
AR
ONE-STAR
NO
-
ST
AR
ONE-STAR
NO
-
ST
AR
ONE-STAR
NO
-
ST
AR
ONE-STAR
NO
-
ST
AR
ONE-STAR
NO
-
ST
AR
ONE-STAR
NO
-
ST
AR
ONE-STAR
NO
-
ST
AR
ONE-STAR
NO
-
ST
AR
ONE-STAR
NO
-
ST
AR
ONE-STAR
NO
-
ST
AR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
—or one of the Four Devas—
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
いやいや 皐月様の座を
奪うことすらもできる
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
or even steal the throne
from Lady Satsuki herself!
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
Yes! I'll become the empress
of Honnouji Academy
そう 本能字学園の
女帝になって—
and indulge in every luxury
this school has to offer!
学園の ぜいの極みを尽くす！
ああ… たまんないわね
I can scarcely wait!
Maiko, it sounds like
you had everyone fooled.
麻衣子 てめえ
とんだ食わせ者(もん)だったみてえだな
Maiko! Return that
uniform to Ryuuko!
（マコ）麻衣子ちゃん！
その制服を流子ちゃんに返して！
You see, putting on
流子ちゃんはね
その制服を着て—
that uniform
and transforming into
半分裸みたいな格好に
変身するのが—
something that
leaves her half-naked
is Ryuuko's only joy in life!
唯一の楽しみなんだよ
Oh, yes! The transformation!
"Life Fiber Synchronize", was it?
そう 変身！ 人衣(じんい)一体だっけ
I'll have to try that
for myself right away!
早速 試さなきゃ
脱ぎっと にゅるっと
Off with this! On with this!
What?!
何！
Get real.
なめんな てめえみたいな腹黒女が
そう簡単に変身できるわけが…
As if a deceitful bitch like you
could transform so easily!
I did it!
（麻衣子）できた！
（流子）ウッソ！
No way!
Life Fiber Synchronize!
Godrobe Senketsu!
人衣一体 神衣鮮血
GODROBE
SENKETSU
Oh, come on!
そ… そんな…
I had so much trouble mastering the
Life Fiber Synchronization, but she just pulled it off!
私でさえ あれだけ
苦労してできた人衣一体を…
How can she do this, Senketsu?!
なぜだ 鮮血
Forgive me, Ryuuko.
This woman has no shame.
（鮮血）すまん 流子
この女 恥を知らない
If it means power—if it means standing on top of the world—
力のためなら
私が頂点に立つためなら
すっぽんぽんにだって
なってやろうじゃない
I'll gladly get as naked
as the day I was born!
Oh, it's flooding into me!
ああ 満ち満ちに
満ち満ちるわ
The strength! The power! The strepower!
力が！ パワーが！
力パワーが！
Now, let's try out
this strepower, shall we?
じゃあ この力パワーを
試してあげましょう もちろん
It's only natural to start
with the weakest one here!
弱いほうからね！
Mako!
（マコ）わ〜！
（流子）マコ！
（麻衣子）くっ フン！
フグッ！ な… なぜだ！
W-What's going on?!
Why won't my body move?!
なぜ体が動かない
（麻衣子）えい えい！ ダメだ
（流子）これは一体…
What the hell?
It's not working!
It's as if my body's turned to stone!
（麻衣子）まるで体が
固まってしまったようだ
Senketsu... Is that you?
鮮血 お前
ああ 何をするつもり？
や… やめて 早まるな
Wh-What do you think you're doing? S-Stop! Let's not be hasty!
I'm so sorry I tricked you!
だ… だまして ごめんなさい
どうした？ 力パワーは
試さないのか？
What's up?
Aren't you going to try out
that "strepower" of yours?
（麻衣子）ヒィ〜
お願い神衣 返すから ヒィ〜！
Please! I'll give back the Godrobe!
Grr! What's wrong
with this stupid outfit?!
もう何なのよ この服
生意気な！ 生意気な！
So uppity! So impertinent!
服が！ こいつが悪い！
この動かない服が！
It's the outfit! It's all
this stupid outfit's fault!
This stupid, broken outfit!
It's freshly cleaned.
下ろしたてだ きっと のりでも
利きすぎているんだろう…
I bet they just used
too much starch.
Right?!
（鮮血）ぶえ〜！
フン 薄汚い血
飲ませやがって！ ペッ！
How dare she make me drink
that grimy blood of hers!
I'm sorry I was late, Ryuuko!
待たせたな 流子
Well, you remained faithful
to me, so all is forgiven.
ああ だけど浮気しなかったから
許してやるよ
ふぎゃ！
Look, Ryuuko! There's only five minutes to go until the start of first period!
見て 流子ちゃん！
始業ベルまで あと５分切ってる
早く行かなきゃ！
We have to hurry!
I don't wanna be late
and get expelled!
私 遅刻して退学なんて
嫌だ 嫌だ 嫌だよ〜
（流子）え？
（マコ）痛てて…
...Ow...
...I hit my head on the air...
（マコ）
く… 空気にぶつかっちゃったよ
...Wh-What the...
（流子）な… 何だ？
（マコ）え… ええ？
（流子）何が どうなってんだ？
What the hell is going on?
Moron!
バ〜カ！ こいつは
こんなこともあろうかと—
This is my ultimate weapon!
私が仕掛けた最終兵器
偽学校さ
I set it up just in case
something like this happened!
A fake school!
...And now...
そして…
（麻衣子）ひょ〜 ホホホ！
もうおしまいだ！
It's all over for you!
Once my fake school trap,
"Return To Start", is activated,
この偽学校
“振り出しに戻る”トラップは—
起動したら最後
誰にも止めることはできない！
no one can stop it!
Like hell it's over!
（流子）冗談じゃねえ！
If you won't tell us how to stop this thing, I'll just have to beat it out of you!
だったら 貴様をもう一度
たたきのめして—
こいつを止める方法を
吐かせるだけだ！
How about now?
（麻衣子）じゃあ これでどう？
（流子）貴様 血迷ったか！
Wait! Are you out of your mind?!
Now that I've failed in
my plan to take the Godrobe,
神衣奪取作戦に失敗した今
せめて風紀部の誇りに懸けて—
I swear on my pride as a
Disciplinary Bureau member
that I will at least see that you are forever
branded as a tardy student, Matoi Ryuuko!
纏流子 貴様たちに遅刻者としての
らく印を押してやる！
It will be Oogure Maiko's
final act of defiance!
それが この大暮麻衣子
最後の意地よ！
All glory to Honnouji Academy!
本能字学園に 栄光あれ〜！
Just kidding!
なんてね
Watch out, Ryuuko! It's coming apart!
流子 気を付けろ！
もう もたないぞ
Ryuuko, help!
（マコ）流子ちゃん 助けて！
Mako!
（流子）マコ！
（鮮血）流子 私を着ろ！
Ryuuko, put me on!
Right, I forgot!
あっ ああ そうだった
Life Fiber Synchronization!
Godrobe Senketsu!
人衣一体 神衣鮮血
GODROBE
SENKETSU
（マコ）うわ〜！
（流子）とうっ！
What the hell?
おいおい 何だよ
これ海だぞ
We drifted out to sea!
振り出しより後ろに
来ちまったじゃねえか
This is way past square one!
You'll never make it
in time, even wearing me.
（鮮血）
さすがに私を着ていても
もう間に合わないな
You'll be late!
遅刻するしかない
O! M! G!
こ〜れ〜は〜！
This station's for the nonstop rope expresso-way to school!
私たち無星生徒では
とても乗れない—
It's for the super rich! We No-Stars
couldn't hope to ride it in a million years!
お金持ち専用の学校直通
ロープセレブウエーの駅
I always wanted to try it sometime!
これ乗ってみたかった〜
What? Nonstop?
（流子）何！ 直通？
（男子生徒）こらこら！
君たち無星… うおっ
Hey! You No-Stars
—aren't allowed in he—
Shut your mouth and take us to
the end of the line! Full throttle!
いいから フルスロットルで
終点まで出せや！
Mako, hurry! Get in!
マコ 早く乗れ！
え？ ロープウエーの
お金払わないと
But we have to pay the ropeway fare!
I don't have my wallet!
うわっ ない！
じゃあ しかたない
There's nothing for it.
I'll just have to leave my precious, precious croquette lunch instead!
大事な大事なお昼のコロッケ
置いてくね
Who cares about that?
Just get in here!
構うことねえから
早く乗ってくれって
Yay! I always wanted
to ride this! Always!
（マコ）わ〜い わ〜い
これ乗りたかったの！
How many minutes are left?!
（流子）あと何分だ？
Just one! In one minute,
we'll be late! And expelled!
（マコ）あと１分
あと１分で遅刻！ 退学！
No way! One minute?!
ウソ！ あと１分？
I'm gonna get us to homeroom
on time if it's the last thing I do!
意地でも遅刻しねえで
ホームルームに
たどりついてやらあ
Curses. I came so close.
チッ！ もう一息のとこだったのに
でもいいわ
今はおとなしくしておいて—
Well, no matter.
I'll play the good
subordinate for now
また新しいチャンスを狙おう
and wait for another
opportunity to present itself.
I heard everything, Oogure!
（蟇郡）全ては
聞かせてもらったぞ 大暮
Master Gamagoori!
（麻衣子）蟇郡様
（蟇郡）神衣をもって
皐月様に取って代わるなど
You thought you could steal the
Godrobe and overthrow Lady Satsuki, eh?
That's far beyond the likes of you!
貴様ごときには ありえない！
...P-Please forgive me...
お… お許しください
Never! You are expelled!
許せん！ 放校だ！
EXPELLED
You don't deserve to
attend Honnouji Academy!
貴様に本能字学園に
通う資格はない！
（蟇郡）とっとと去れ！
（麻衣子）あっ ああ…
Get out of my sight!
...Damn that Matoi...
（蟇郡）纏め
Thirty seconds!
（マコ）あと30秒！
Got it!
（流子）わかってら
駅に降りてる暇はねえ！
There's no time to
get out at the station!
でえい！
Let's see, next up is... Matoi.
（美木杉(みきすぎ)）え〜 次 纏君
纏流子…
Matoi Ryuuko.
え〜 纏流子君
Matoi Ryuuko?
（流子）ハァ…
Present.
はい
Before the bell rings
chime ga naru mae ni
I sneak out of school
kugurinuketa
Avoiding the adults' vacant stares
otonatachi no haiiro no me
The pointless conversations
tawai no nai kaiwa
Keep going on and on
togirenu mama
As I walk down the slope
sakamichi wo kudatteku
I have nothing to do
nani wo suru demo naku
And nowhere to go
yuku ate sae mo naku
Right now, all I do
tada atashi ima wa ne
Is ignore any and all warnings
donna chuukoku mo mimi wo surinukeru
Because I still want to be free
mada mada suki ni sasete
I'm sorry, but it's not like me
gomen ne e ni kaita you na
To be an exemplary student
yuutosei wa rashiku nai wa
So I undo two of my shirt buttons
shirt no button wo futatsu hazushite
And take the back alley
rojiura no nukemichi
A path of mysterious sweet temptation
amai yuuwaku wa michi
Some things I've kept hidden from everyone
dare ni mo mada hanashite nai
But tonight, I will reveal my secrets to you
atashi no himitsu wo kon'ya oshiete ageru
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
（鮮血）その男は寡黙
The man remains silent.
SILENT
追い詰めた獲物に対して
ただひと言 こう告げる—
He says but one thing, and it is to
his prey when he has them cornered.
PREY
BUT ONE THING
SAYS
“服を脱げ”
"TAKE OFF YOUR CLOTHES"
"Take off your clothes."
Next time on KILL la KILL, "Trigger".
次回 キルラキル「銃爪(ヒキガネ)」
EPISODE 5
TRIGGER